Louise Z. Young Photographs MS156
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Negatives and Prints, 1947 -- 1970; MS156.001; 1.0 Linear Feet; 498 Digital Object(s)
  - Hodgdon and Carmichael Hall - Interiors, 1954; MS156.001.001.00024 (Box 1)
    - Students eating in Carmichael dining hall, 1954-09-23; MS156.001.001.00024.00019; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Also exists as: UA136.002.DO.00862.
      Buildings; Food service; Interior views; Students
  - Copies of Past Presidents of Tufts, 1954; MS156.001.001.00025 (Box 1)
    - President Hosea Ballou 2nd, 1853-1861, 1954-10-28; MS156.001.001.00025.00001; Unknown (Box 1)
      Also exists as: UA136.002.DO.01279.
      College presidents; Portraits; Ballou, Hosea, 2d
    - President Alonzo A. Miner, 1862-1875, 1954-10-28; MS156.001.001.00025.00002; Unknown (Box 1)
      Also exists as: UA001.002.004.00001.00001.
      College presidents; Portraits; Miner, Alonzo Ames
    - President Elmer H. Capen, 1875-1905, 1954-10-28; MS156.001.001.00025.00003; Unknown (Box 1)
      Also exists as: MS054.003.DO.02221.
      College presidents; Portraits; Capen, Elmer Hewitt
    - President Frederick W. Hamilton, 1906-1912, 1954-10-28; MS156.001.001.00025.00004; Unknown (Box 1)
      Also exists as: UA001.004.DO.00087.
      College presidents; Portraits; Hamilton, Frederick William
    - President Hermon Carey Bumpus, 1914-1919, 1954-10-28; MS156.001.001.00025.00005; Unknown (Box 1)
      Also exists as: UA001.006.002.00002.00001.
      College presidents; Portraits; Bumpus, Hermon Carey
    - President John Albert Cousens, 1920-1937, 1954-10-28; MS156.001.001.00025.00006; Unknown (Box 1)
      College presidents; Portraits; Cousens, John Albert
    - Acting President William Leslie Hooper, 1954-10-28; MS156.001.001.00025.00007; Unknown (Box 1)
      Also exists as: UA136.002.DO.02874.
      College presidents; Portraits; Hooper, Willliam Leslie
  - Honoraries, 1954 -- 1955; MS156.001.001.00026 (Box 1)
    - Honorary degree recipient Nellie Reynolds, 1954-10-28; MS156.001.001.00026.00001; Unknown (Box 1)
      Portraits; Reynolds, Nellie
    - Honorary degree recipient Reverend Laurance Irving Neale, 1955-05-24; MS156.001.001.00026.00002; Unknown (Box 1)
      Portraits; Neale, Laurance Irving
    - Honorary degree recipient Rear Admiral Bartholomew W. Hogan, 1955-05-24; MS156.001.001.00026.00003; Unknown (Box 1)
      Portraits; Hogan, Bartholomew W.
    - Honorary degree recipient Carl Sandburg, 1955-05-24; MS156.001.001.00026.00004; Unknown (Box 1)
      Portraits; Sandburg, Carl, 1878-1967
    - Harold W. Besse, President of the Boston Stock Exchange, 1955-05-24; MS156.001.001.00026.00005; Unknown (Box 1)
      Portraits
    - Honorary degree recipient Alvin J. Bennett, 1955-05-24; MS156.001.001.00026.00006; Unknown (Box 1)
      Portraits; Bennett, Alvin J.
    - Honorary degree Margaret Chase Smith, 1955-05-24; MS156.001.001.00026.00007; Shoaf, Robert (Box 1)
      Portraits; Smith, Margaret Chase
  - Commencement - Tufts, 1955; MS156.001.001.00027 (Box 1)
    - Carl Sandburg with John Holmes at Commencement, 1955-06-12; MS156.001.001.00027.00001; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Sandburg, Carl, 1878-1967; Holmes, John
    - Dean Wessell, Arthur J. Anderson, and Carl Sandburg at Commencement, 1955-06-12; MS156.001.001.00027.00002; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Commencement; Honorary degrees; Sandburg, Carl, 1878-1967; Anderson, Arthur J.
    - Arthur J. Anderson and Carl Sandburg at Commencement, 1955-06-12; MS156.001.001.00027.00003; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Commencement; Honorary degrees; Sandburg, Carl, 1878-1967; Anderson, Arthur J.; Wessell, Nils Yngve
    - 1955 honorary degree recipients at Commencement, 1955-06-12; MS156.001.001.00027.00004; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Commencement; Honorary degrees; Portraits, Group
    - Carl Sandburg receiving hood and honorary degree at Commencement, 1955-06-12; MS156.001.001.00027.00005; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Commencement; Honorary degrees; Sandburg, Carl, 1878-1967
    - Nellie Reynolds receiving hood and honorary degree at Commencement, 1955-06-12; MS156.001.001.00027.00006; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Commencement; Honorary degrees; Reynolds, Nellie
    - Wilfred McGregor Hall receiving hood and honorary degree at Commencement, 1955-06-12; MS156.001.001.00027.00007; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Commencement; Honorary degrees; Hall, Wilfred McGregor
    - Rear Admiral Bartholomew W. Hogan receiving hood and honorary degree at Commencement, 1955-06-12; MS156.001.001.00027.00008; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Commencement; Honorary degrees; Hogan, Bartholomew W.
    - Harold Edward Sweet receiving hood and honorary degree at Commencement, 1955-06-12; MS156.001.001.00027.00009; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Commencement; Honorary degrees; Sweet, Harold Edward
    - Harvey Eastman Averill receiving hood and honorary degree at Commencement, 1955-06-12; MS156.001.001.00027.00010; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Commencement; Honorary degrees; Averill, Harvey Eastman
    - Margaret Chase Smith receiving hood and honorary degree at Commencement, 1955-06-12; MS156.001.001.00027.00011; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Commencement; Honorary degrees; Smith, Margaret Chase
    - Alvin J. Bennett receiving hood and honorary degree at Commencement, 1955-06-12; MS156.001.001.00027.00012; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Commencement; Honorary degrees; Bennett, Alvin J.
    - Dana Meserve Cotton receiving hood and honorary degree at Commencement, 1955-06-12; MS156.001.001.00027.00013; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Commencement; Honorary degrees; Cotton, Dana Merserve
    - Edward Benno Hanify receiving hood and honorary degree at Commencement, 1955-06-12; MS156.001.001.00027.00014; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Commencement; Honorary degrees; Hanify, Edward Benno
    - Laurance Irving Neale with Ralph Williams at Commencement, 1955-06-12; MS156.001.001.00027.00015; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Commencement; Honorary degrees; Neale, Laurance Irving; Williams, Ralph
  - Cohen Auditorium, 1955; MS156.001.001.00028 (Box 1)
    - Cohen Arts Center entrance, 1955-10-04; MS156.001.001.00028.00001; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
    - Left angle view of Cohen Arts Center, 1955-10-04; MS156.001.001.00028.00002; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
  - Robert Frost, 1955; MS156.001.001.00029 (Box 1)
    - Robert Frost shaking hands with student, 1955-10-18; MS156.001.001.00029.00001; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Students; Frost, Robert, 1874-1963
    - Robert Frost speaking with student, 1955-10-18; MS156.001.001.00029.00002; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Students; Books; Frost, Robert, 1874-1963
    - Robert Frost speaking with John Holmes, 1955-10-18; MS156.001.001.00029.00003; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Also exists as: MS007.010.DO.00190.
      Frost, Robert, 1874-1963; Holmes, John
  - Sweet Hall - Tufts University, 1955; MS156.001.001.00030 (Box 1)
    - Right angle view of Sweet Hall, 1955-11-13; MS156.001.001.00030.00001; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
  - Honoraries - Tufts '55 Convocation, 1955; MS156.001.001.00031 (Box 1)
    - Convocation honorary degree recipient Dr. Nathan M. Pusey, 1955-11-15; MS156.001.001.00031.00001; Bachrach, Fabian (Box 1)
      Portraits; Pusey, Nathan M. (Nathan Marsh), 1907-2001
    - Convocation honorary degree recipient James W. Wickenden, 1955-11-15; MS156.001.001.00031.00002; Unknown (Box 1)
      Portraits; Wickenden, James W.
    - Convocation honorary degree recipient Joseph Garland, M.D., 1955-11-15; MS156.001.001.00031.00003; Unknown (Box 1)
      Portraits; Garland, Joseph
    - Convocation honorary degree recipient Reverend Joseph R. N. Maxwell, 1955-11-15; MS156.001.001.00031.00004; Bachrach, Fabian (Box 1)
      Portraits; Maxwell, Joseph R.N.
    - Convocation honorary degree recipient Dr. Barnaby C. Keeney, 1955-11-15; MS156.001.001.00031.00005; Unknown (Box 1)
      Portraits; Keeney, Barnaby C. (Barnaby Conrad), 1914-1980
    - Convocation honorary degree recipient George Roy Elliot, 1955-11-15; MS156.001.001.00031.00006; Unknown (Box 1)
      Portraits; Elliot, George Roy
    - Convocation honorary degree recipient Mary Elizabeth Switzer, 1955-11-15; MS156.001.001.00031.00007; Unknown (Box 1)
      Portraits; Switzer, Mary Elizabeth, 1900-
    - Convocation honorary degree recipient Angus H. Maclean, 1955-11-15; MS156.001.001.00031.00008; Unknown (Box 1)
      Portraits; MacLean, Angus Hector, 1892-1969
    - Convocation honorary degree recipient Hollis L. Caswell, 1955-11-15; MS156.001.001.00031.00009; Bachrach, Fabian (Box 1)
      Portraits; Caswell, Hollis L. (Hollis Leland), 1901-1988
    - Convocation honorary degree recipient Lewis L. Strauss, 1955-11-15; MS156.001.001.00031.00010; Unknown (Box 1)
      Portraits; Strauss, Lewis L.
    - Convocation honorary degree recipient Dr. Abram L. Sachar, 1955-11-15; MS156.001.001.00031.00011; Unknown (Box 1)
      Portraits; Sachar, Abram Leon, 1899-1993
    - Convocation honorary degree recipient Roy E. Larsen, 1955-11-15; MS156.001.001.00031.00012; Unknown (Box 1)
      Portraits; Larsen, Roy E. (Roy Edward), b. 1899
    - Convocation honorary degree recipient Ernest H. Wilkins, 1955-11-15; MS156.001.001.00031.00013; Unknown (Box 1)
      Portraits; Wilkins, Ernest Hatch, 1880-1966
    - Convocation honorary degree recipient James R. Killian, Jr., 1955-11-15; MS156.001.001.00031.00014; Unknown (Box 1)
      Portraits; Killian, James Rhyne, 1904-1988
    - Convocation honorary degree recipient Dr. Arthur S. Fleming, 1955-11-15; MS156.001.001.00031.00015; Unknown (Box 1)
      Portraits; Fleming, Arthur S.
    - Convocation honorary degree recipient Marion B. Folsom, 1955-11-15; MS156.001.001.00031.00016; Unknown (Box 1)
      Portraits; Folsom, Marion Bayard, 1893-1976
  - Honoraries - Tufts, 1956; MS156.001.001.00032 (Box 1)
    - Honorary degree recipient Dr. Charles Munch, 1956-05-23; MS156.001.001.00032.00001; Unknown (Box 1)
      Portraits; Munch, Charles, 1891-1968
    - Honorary degree recipient Dean Nancy Duke Lewis, 1956-05-23; MS156.001.001.00032.00002; Unknown (Box 1)
      Portraits; Lewis, Nancy Duke
    - Honorary degree recipient John Moors Cabot, 1956-05-23; MS156.001.001.00032.00003; Unknown (Box 1)
      Portraits; Cabot, John Moors
    - Honorary degree recipient Nelson W. Aldrich, 1956-05-23; MS156.001.001.00032.00004; Unknown (Box 1)
      Portraits; Aldrich, Nelson W.
    - Honorary degree recipient Dr. Max Tishler, 1956-05-23; MS156.001.001.00032.00005; Unknown (Box 1)
      Portraits; Tishler, Max
    - Honorary degree recipient Dr. John T. Blake, 1956-05-23; MS156.001.001.00032.00006; Unknown (Box 1)
      Portraits; Blake, John Twiss
    - Honorary degree recipient Reverend Arthur W. Webster, 1956-05-23; MS156.001.001.00032.00007; Unknown (Box 1)
      Portraits; Webster, Arthur W.
    - Honorary degree recipient Henry Ray Aldrich, 1956-05-23; MS156.001.001.00032.00008; Unknown (Box 1)
      Portraits; Aldrich, Henry R. (Henry Ray), b. 1891
    - Honorary degree recipient Theodore Warren Hodges, 1956-05-23; MS156.001.001.00032.00009; Unknown (Box 1)
      Portraits; Hodges, Theodore Warren
  - Tufts Commencement, 1956; MS156.001.001.00033 (Box 1)
    - Max Tishler receiving hood and honorary degree at Commencement, 1956-06-10; MS156.001.001.00033.00001; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Commencement; Honorary degrees; Tishler, Max
    - Nancy Duke Lewis receiving hood and honorary degree at Commencement, 1956-06-10; MS156.001.001.00033.00002; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Commencement; Honorary degrees; Lewis, Nancy Duke
    - John Moors Cabot receiving hood and honorary degree at Commencement, 1956-06-10; MS156.001.001.00033.00003; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Commencement; Honorary degrees; Cabot, John Moors
    - Joseph Morton receiving hood and honorary degree at Commencement, 1956-06-10; MS156.001.001.00033.00004; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Commencement; Honorary degrees; Morton, Joseph W.
    - Henry Ray Aldrich receiving hood and honorary degree at Commencement, 1956-06-10; MS156.001.001.00033.00005; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Commencement; Honorary degrees; Aldrich, Henry R. (Henry Ray), b. 1891
    - John Twiss Blake receiving hood and honorary degree at Commencement, 1956-06-10; MS156.001.001.00033.00006; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Commencement; Honorary degrees; Blake, John Twiss
    - Clarence Cassidy receiving hood and honorary degree at Commencement, 1956-06-10; MS156.001.001.00033.00007; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Commencement; Honorary degrees; Cassidy, Clarence
    - Arthur Fleming receiving hood and honorary degree at Commencement, 1956-06-10; MS156.001.001.00033.00008; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Commencement; Honorary degrees; Fleming, Arthur S.
    - Weston Howland receiving hood and honorary degree at Commencement, 1956-06-10; MS156.001.001.00033.00009; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Commencement; Honorary degrees; Howland, Weston
    - Charles Munch receiving hood and honorary degree at Commencement, 1956-06-10; MS156.001.001.00033.00010; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Commencement; Honorary degrees; Munch, Charles, 1891-1968
    - Lewis Strauss receiving hood and honorary degree at Commencement, 1956-06-10; MS156.001.001.00033.00011; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Commencement; Honorary degrees; Strauss, Lewis L.
    - Arthur Webster receiving hood and honorary degree at Commencement, 1956-06-10; MS156.001.001.00033.00012; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Commencement; Honorary degrees; Webster, Arthur W.
    - Theodore Hodges receiving hood and honorary degree at Commencement, 1956-06-10; MS156.001.001.00033.00013; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Commencement; Honorary degrees; Hodges, Theodore Warren
    - Group of honorary degree recipients at Commencement, 1956-06-10; MS156.001.001.00033.00014; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
    - John Moors Cabot speaking at Commencement, 1956-06-10; MS156.001.001.00033.00015; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Commencement; Speeches; Cabot, John Moors
    - Nils Wessell, John Moors Cabot, and Arthur J. Anderson at Commencement, 1956-06-10; MS156.001.001.00033.00016; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Commencement; Wessell, Nils Yngve; Cabot, John Moors; Anderson, Arthur J.
    - Nancy Duke Lewis and Nils Wessell at Commencement, 1956-06-10; MS156.001.001.00033.00017; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Commencement; Wessell, Nils Yngve; Lewis, Nancy Duke
    - Charles Munch at Commencement (other man identified as McKillop), 1956-06-10; MS156.001.001.00033.00018; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Commencement; Munch, Charles
    - Commencement marshals, 1956-06-10; MS156.001.001.00033.00019; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
    - John Moors Cabot and Dean Stuart at Commencement, 1956-06-10; MS156.001.001.00033.00020; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Commencement; College administrators; Cabot, John Moors; Stewart, Robert B.
    - Arthur J. Anderson and Professor Busch at Commencement, 1956-06-10; MS156.001.001.00033.00021; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Commencement; Anderson, Arthur J.
    - Commencement audience, 1956-06-10; MS156.001.001.00033.00022; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
  - Exteriors - Tufts Campus, 1956; MS156.001.001.00034 (Box 1)
    - Professors Row, 1956-07-19; MS156.001.001.00034.00001; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Trees; Sidewalks
    - Fraternity houses on Professors Row, 1956-07-19; MS156.001.001.00034.00002; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Also exists as: UA136.002.DO.00824.
      Fraternities; Greek letter societies
    - Exterior view of Braker Hall, 1956-07-19; MS156.001.001.00034.00003; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
    - View of East Hall through trees, 1956-07-19; MS156.001.001.00034.00004; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
    - View of Eaton Hall and War Memorial Library through trees, 1956-07-19; MS156.001.001.00034.00005; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
    - Exterior view of West Hall, 1956-07-19; MS156.001.001.00034.00006; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
  - Engineering Buildings, 1956; MS156.001.001.00035 (Box 1)
    - Robinson Hall from behind old engineering building, 1956-09-13; MS156.001.001.00035.00001; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
    - Engineering buildings on Boston Avenue, 1956-09-13; MS156.001.001.00035.00002; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Buildings; Exterior views; Laboratories
    - Rear view of Bromfield-Pearson, 1956-09-13; MS156.001.001.00035.00003; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
    - Exterior view of Robinson Hall, 1956-09-13; MS156.001.001.00035.00004; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
    - Howe Mechanical Engineering Building, 1956-09-13; MS156.001.001.00035.00005; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Also exists as: UA136.002.DO.00422.
    - Exterior view of Halligan Hall, 1956-09-13; MS156.001.001.00035.00006; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Also exists as: UA136.002.DO.00964.
    - Interior view of engineeering classroom, 1956-09-13; MS156.001.001.00035.00007; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
    - Mechanical laboratory in engineering building, 1956-09-13; MS156.001.001.00035.00008; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Buildings; Interior views; Engineering; Machinery
  - Exterior - Cohen and Alumni Hall for Bookstore, 1956; MS156.001.001.00036 (Box 1)
    - Exterior view of Cohen Arts Center and Alumni Hall, 1956-09-26; MS156.001.001.00036.00001; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Cohen Arts Center --Alumni Hall; Buildings --Exterior views; negatives (photographic)
  - Robert Frost - Tufts, 1956; MS156.001.001.00037 (Box 1)
    - Robert Frost signing book and speaking with student, 1956-11-14; MS156.001.001.00037.00001; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Students; negatives (photographic); Frost, Robert
    - Robert Frost speaking with Jackson student, 1956-11-14; MS156.001.001.00037.00002; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
  - Exteriors for Lampshade, 1956; MS156.001.001.00038 (Box 1)
    - Alumni Gate with car in drive, 1956; MS156.001.001.00038.00001; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Picture taken for lampshade
      Alumni Gate --Gates; negatives (photographic)
    - Gager Gate with West Hall, 1956; MS156.001.001.00038.00002; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      West Hall --Gager Gate; Gates; negatives (photographic)
    - Gager Gate with West Hall, 1956; MS156.001.001.00038.00003; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
    - Gager Gate, 1956; MS156.001.001.00038.00004; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Gager Gate; Gates; negatives (photographic)
    - Carmichael Hall spire, 1956; MS156.001.001.00038.00005; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Carmicheal Hall; Exterior views; negatives (photographic)
    - Close view of Alumni Gate, 1956; MS156.001.001.00038.00006; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Alumni Gate; Gates; negatives (photographic)
    - Gager Gate, 1956; MS156.001.001.00038.00007; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
    - Alumni Gate, 1956; MS156.001.001.00038.00008; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
  - Exterior Carmichael Hall, 1956 -- 1957; MS156.001.001.00039 (Box 1)
    - Carmichael Hall viewed through Gager Gate, 1956; MS156.001.001.00039.00001; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Carmicheal Hall; Exterior views --Gates; negatives (photographic)
  - Dr. Carpenter and Jumbo, 1957; MS156.001.001.00040 (Box 1)
    - Russell Carpenter seated in front of Jumbo holding copy of Puck magazine, 1957-05-10; MS156.001.001.00040.00001; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Barnum Museum of Natural History; negatives (photographic); Jumbo --Carpenter, Russell L.
  - Commencement - Tufts, 1957; MS156.001.001.00041 (Box 1)
    - Group of honorary degree recipients at Commencement, 1957-06-09; MS156.001.001.00041.00001; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Commencement --Portraits, Group; negatives (photographic); Wessell, Nils Yngve --Washburn, Bradford, 1910-2007
    - Julius Haller receiving hood and honorary degree at Commencement, 1957-06-09; MS156.001.001.00041.00002; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Commencement --Honorary degrees; negatives (photographic); Wessell, Nils Yngve --Haller, Julius
    - Hanson Baldwin receiving hood and honorary degree at Commencement, 1957-06-09; MS156.001.001.00041.00003; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Commencement --Honorary degrees; negatives (photographic); Wessell, Nils Yngve --Baldwin, Hanson Weightman, 1903-1991
    - Frederic Church receiving hood and honorary degree at Commencement, 1957-06-09; MS156.001.001.00041.00004; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Commencement --Honorary degrees; negatives (photographic); Wessell, Nils Yngve --Church, Frederic
    - George E. Rogers receiving hood and honorary degree at Commencement, 1957-06-09; MS156.001.001.00041.00005; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Commencement --Honorary degrees; negatives (photographic); Wessell, Nils Yngve --Rogers, George E.
    - Deane Winthrop True receiving hood and honorary degree at Commencement, 1957-06-09; MS156.001.001.00041.00006; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Commencement --Honorary degrees; negatives (photographic); Wessell, Nils Yngve --True, Deane Winthrop
    - John Prescott Robertson receiving hood and honorary degree at Commencement, 1957-06-09; MS156.001.001.00041.00007; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Commencement --Honorary degrees; negatives (photographic); Wessell, Nils Yngve --Robertson, John Prescott
    - Earl Warren receiving hood and honorary degree at Commencement, 1957-06-09; MS156.001.001.00041.00008; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Commencement --Honorary degrees; negatives (photographic); Wessell, Nils Yngve --Warren, Earl
    - S. Bruce Black receiving hood and honorary degree at Commencement, 1957-06-09; MS156.001.001.00041.00009; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Commencement --Honorary degrees; negatives (photographic); Wessell, Nils Yngve --Black, S. Bruce
    - H. Bradford Washburn receiving hood and honorary degree at Commencement, 1957-06-09; MS156.001.001.00041.00010; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Commencement --Honorary degrees; negatives (photographic); Wessell, Nils Yngve --Washburn, Bradford, 1910-2007
    - H. Bradford Washburn speaking at Commencement, 1957-06-09; MS156.001.001.00041.00011; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Commencement --Speeches --Washburn, H. Bradford; negatives (photographic); Wessell, Nils Yngve --Washburn, Bradford, 1910-2007
    - 3 Swedes,' Nils Wessel, Earl Warren, and Arthur J. Anderson at Commencement, 1957-06-09; MS156.001.001.00041.00012; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Commencement; negatives (photographic); Wessell, Nils Yngve --Warren, Earl --Anderson, Arthur J.
    - Earl Warren, Robert Meserve, and Dean Stewart at Commencement, 1957-06-09; MS156.001.001.00041.00013; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Commencement --Warren, Earl --Meserue --Stewart; negatives (photographic); Stewart, Robert B. --Meserve, Robert W. --Warren, Earl
    - Honorees and marshal at Commencement, 1957-06-09; MS156.001.001.00041.00014; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Men identified as Busch, Reynolds, Fine, and Williams.
      Commencement; negatives (photographic); Wessell, Nils Yngve --Reynolds, Joel Warren
    - Dean Emery with Hanson Baldwin at Commencement, 1957-06-09; MS156.001.001.00041.00015; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Commencement; negatives (photographic); Baldwin, Hanson Weightman, 1903-1991 --Emery, Clifton W.
    - Earl Warren, Nils Wessel, and H. Bradford Washburn at Commencement, 1957-06-09; MS156.001.001.00041.00016; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Commencement; negatives (photographic); Wessell, Nils Yngve --Washburn, Bradford, 1910-2007 --Warren, Earl
    - Earl Warren and Arthur J. Anderson at Commencement, 1957-06-09; MS156.001.001.00041.00017; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Commencement; negatives (photographic); Warren, Earl --Anderson, Arthur J.